Wooden Floor Pack

This pack contains 45 different textures spread over 5 different wood types.
It also contain Specular and Normal map.

In Materials folder you find materials that is ready to be use.
Just apply the material in your scene to use it.

In root folder you find a image that will show how to set a custom material.

If you have questions, feedback or just want to chat. Contact me at: mail@parlinde.com

Best regards Lindesign